Guide to the Wilkins Media Company Records, 1967-1998 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Wilkins Media Company records 1967-1998 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Wilkins Media Company
13.5 linear feet Extent: 13400 Items
Wilkins Media Company is an outdoor advertising company based in Atlanta, Georgia. Founded in 1965 as Southern Outdoor Markets, the company changed its name in 1974 to Associates of the Bell Company. In 1987 Bill Wilkins purchased the company, changing the name to Wilkins Outdoor Network. The name changed again in 1999 to Wilkins Media Company. The Wilkins Media Company Records span the years 1967-1998 and include slides, photographs, presentation scripts, audio and video cassettes, brochures, pamphlets and publications related to Wilkins Media Company's activities as well as to the outdoor advertising industry in general. Represented are materials from the Institute of Outdoor Advertising, Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Patrick Media Group, Traffic Audit Bureau, Metromedia Technologies and Naegele Advertising Companies. Companies represented include Dole, Ford, Pacific Gas and Electric (PG&E) and Toyota. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.01384
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Wilkins Media Company Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift from 2002-2005.
Historical Note
Founded in 1965 as Southern Outdoor Markets, the company changed its name in 1974 to Associates of the Bell Company. In 1987 Bill Wilkins purchased the company, changing the name to Wilkins Outdoor Network. The name changed again in 1999 to Wilkins Media Company.
Source: Wilkins Media website
Collection Overview
The Wilkins Media Company Records span the years 1967-1998 and include slides, photographs, presentation scripts, audio and video cassettes, brochures, pamphlets and publications related to the company's activities as well as to the outdoor advertising industry in general. Represented are materials from the Institute of Outdoor Advertising, Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Patrick Media Group, Traffic Audit Bureau, Metromedia Technologies and Naegele Advertising Companies. Companies represented include Dole, Ford, Pacific Gas and Electric (PG&E) and Toyota.
Collection Arrangement
The Collection is arranged into five series: Slides; Photographs; Printed Material; Audiovisual Materials; and Oversized Materials. Slides is comprised of color slides of billboards and other outdoor advertising in a variety of locations, predominantly in the United States. Photographs contain color print photographs of billboards and other outdoor advertizing. Printed Material contains brochures, pamplets, posters, industry publications, price guides, presentation scripts, and other printed material from a variety of sources. Audiovisual Materials contains video cassettes and one audio cassette, from a variety of producers. Most items are related to advertising and outdoor advertising. Oversized Materials contains large format materials removed from previous series.
Subject Headings
Wilkins, William N.; Wilkins Media Company; Dole Food Company; Ford Motor Company; Institute of Outdoor Advertising; Metromedia, Inc.; Naegele Advertising Companies (Minneapolis, Minn.); Outdoor Advertising Association of America; Pacific Gas and Electric Company; Toyota Motor Sales, U.S.A., Inc.; Advertising, Outdoor -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Atlanta (Ga.) -- Commerce; Billboards; Slides; Photographs; Audiocassettes; Videocassettes; Atlanta (Ga.); John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related materials may be found the following Hartman Center collections:
Duplex Outdoor Advertising Billboard Images and Records
Gaess Outdoor Advertising Photographs
Garrett Orr Papers
Howard Scott Papers
Ohio Outdoor Advertising Corporation Records
Outdoor Advertising Association of Connecticut Records
Outdoor Advertising Association of America Archives
Outdoor Advertising Association of America Slide Library
Porter Advertising Billboard Sketches
R.C. Maxwell Company Records
Detailed Description of Collection
- Slides, 1960-1996 and undated, (11 boxes)
  Contains color slides of billboards and other outdoor advertising in a variety of locations, predominantly in the United States. Slides are arranged as received. Some have been removed from original containers; folder titles reflect original labeling.
  - 030920 extra set, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 1)
  - Auto slides, circa late 1960s-early 1970s (Box 1)
  - Auto slides, 1968 Aug.-1972 Apr. (Box 1)
  - Auto slides and miscellaneous, 1972 July (Box 1)
  - Bill's creative slides 1/96, circa 1984-1996 (Box 1)
  - Bill's slide files Categories, circa 1980s (Box 1)
  - Bill's slide files Creative, circa 1980s (Box 1)
  - Bill's slide files MMT, circa 1989 (Box 1)
  - Bill's slide files Presentation, circa late 1970s-1988 (Box 1)
  - Bill's slide files Won Acct., circa 1980s (Box 1)
  - Bill's slide files Won Basic, 1983-1989 (Box 2)
  - Cars--Coming & Going, 1968 July (Box 2)
  - Creative slides, circa 1970s-early 1990s (Box 2)
  - Creative slides, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 2)
  - Creative surge-duplicates, 1988 Sept. (Box 2)
  - Dole, circa late 1980s-early 1990s (Box 2)
  - FDAF slide presentation plus spares, miscellaneous billboards, circa 1979 (Box 2)
  - Ford slides (Texas), 1972 July (Box 2)
  - Ford Slides--Texas, circa 1972 (Box 2)
  - Hastings slides, 1977-1986 (Box 2)
  - It Pays To Be Creative tray #1, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 2)
  - It Pays To Be Creative tray #2, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 2)
  - J. W. Robinson complete set ABC, 1986 Sept. (Box 3)
  - Miliken slides, undated (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous and copies, 1974 May (Box 3)
  - MMT slide presentation, 1989 June (Box 3)
  - Naegele/Lamar Dean/Standish-Johnson miscellaneous, circa 1970s (Box 3)
  - Omaha, circa 1980s (Box 3)
  - Omaha Ad Club 1989 creative presentation, circa 1972-1989 (Box 3)
  - Other media, circa 1984-1990 (Box 3)
  - Outdoor: A Creative Renaissance, circa 1980s (Box 3)
  - Outdoor: The Retailers' Media Revolution, circa 1970s (Box 3)
  - Outdoor advertising, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 3)
  - Outdoor advertising--Dole, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Outdoor advertising--various companies and miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 3)
  - Outdoor for Life Insurance, circa 1970s (Box 4)
  - Outdoor promotional slides--miscellaneous, undated (Box 4)
  - Out-of-Home media and lotteries--New Orleans, 1995 Jan. 1 (Box 4)
  - Partial FDAF presentation--Nestlé's creative savings--soft drink, circa late 1960s-1970s (Box 4)
  - PG&E slides--Foster & Kleiser 1979, circa 1978-1979 (Box 4)
  - Phoenix, circa 1970s-1980s, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Publix stretch vinyls (#1914, #54345), circa 1980s (Box 4)
  - Sights & Sounds, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 4)
  - Slide show, circa 1986-1989 (Box 4)
  - Slides for bew'l file, 1974-1988 (Box 5)
  - The Media's Medium-Phoenix Ad Club, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 5)
  - Toyota designs & cars, circa 1970s (Box 5)
  - Unlabeled slide show, circa 1960s (Box 5)
  - Unlabeled slide show, circa 1970s (Box 5)
  - Why Outdoor in the South, 1969 Nov. (Box 5)
  - Wilkins Outdoor--miscellaneous, circa 1988 (Box 5)
  - Unsorted slides, 1960s-1990s, (1-2 of 40 folders) (Box 5)
  - Unsorted slides, 1960s-1990s (continued), (3-8 of 40 folders) (Box 6)
  - Unsorted slides, 1960s-1990s (continued), (9-14 of 40 folders) (Box 7)
  - Unsorted slides, 1960s-1990s (continued), (15-20 of 40 folders) (Box 8)
  - Unsorted slides, 1960s-1990s (continued), (21-26 of 40 folders) (Box 9)
  - Unsorted slides, 1960s-1990s (continued), (27-32 of 40 folders) (Box 10)
  - Unsorted slides, 1960s-1990s (continued), (33-40 of 40 folders) (Box 11)
- Photographs, 1986-1991, (4 boxes)
  Contains color photographs of billboards and other outdoor advertisements. Folder titles reflect original labeling.
  - Buses, circa late 1980s-early 1990s (Box 12)
  - Creative contest, 1986-1989, (1-6 of 16 folders) (Box 12)
  - Creative contest, 1986-1989 (continued), (7-12 of 16 folders) (Box 13)
  - Creative contest, 1986-1989 (continued), (13-16 of 16 folders) (Box 14)
  - Photograph album--WON outdoor, circa 1989, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Photograph album--third annual Knoxville meeting, circa 1989 Dec. (Box 14)
  - Unsorted photographs, circa 1990 (Box 14)
  - Photographs and forms, 1988-1991 (Box 15)
  - Photographs from ABC photograph and slide file, 1988 July (Box 15)
  - Unsorted photographs, 1970s-circa 1990, (2 folders) (Box 15)
- Printed Material, 1967-1988 and undated, (5 boxes)
  Includes brochures, pamphlets, posters, industry publications, price guides, presentation scripts, and other printed material from a variety of sources. Publishers include the Institute of Outdoor Advertising, Metromedia Technologies, the Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Outdoor Network USA, Patrick Media Group and Traffic Audit Bureau. Grouped by publisher and organized alphabetically by title.
  - Christmas cards, undated (Box 16)
  - Clippings, 1987-1989 and undated (Box 16)
  - Correspondence, 1987 Aug.-1990 July (Box 16)
  - Creative contest materials, 1987 Sept.-1987 Nov. and undated (Box 16)
  - Demographic profiles, circa 1990s
    - Activity drinks (Box 16)
    - Auto dealers (Box 16)
    - Bottled water (Box 16)
    - Breakfast foods (Box 16)
    - Building supplies (Box 16)
    - Cable television (Box 16)
    - Commercial and savings banks (Box 16)
    - Cruise vacations (Box 16)
    - Dairy (Box 16)
    - Department stores (Box 16)
    - Fast food restaurants (Box 16)
    - Hair care (Box 16)
    - Men 18-34 (Box 16)
    - Restaurants (Box 17)
    - Supermarkets (Box 17)
    - Travel (Box 17)
  - Institute of Outdoor Advertising, 1967-1988 and undated
    - Brochures and reports, 1967-1988 and undated
      - All Roads Leading to Palm Springs..., undated (Box 17)
      - All Sales Are As Local As..., undated (Box 17)
      - An Important Announcement from Bill Wersell of Toledo, Ohio, undated (Box 17)
      - Before Outdoor We Sold 91 CB Radios, circa 1970s (Box 17)
      - Best of Outdoor--Book II, circa 1980s (Box 17)
      - Big Outdoor, undated (Box 17)
      - Bring Out Your Best, undated (Box 17)
      - Can You Outdo This Outdoor, 1987 Dec. 14 (Box 17)
      - Clark Dared to Be Different, circa 1980s (Box 17)
      - Creative Guide to Outdoor Advertising, undated (Box 17)
      - Enjoy the Great Outdoors, undated (Box 17)
      - Every Student Places Our Outdoor..., 1976 Sept. (Box 17)
      - First Medium, 1975 (Box 17)
      - For Its Merchandising Value, 1977 Mar. (Box 17)
      - Furs by Weiss, undated (Box 17)
      - Grain Belt Has Had Sales Increases..., undated (Box 17)
      - Help Wanted, undated (Box 17)
      - How Does HBO Spell, Local Marketing Success, undated (Box 17)
      - If You'd Like to Give Your Advertising a Lift..., undated (Box 17)
      - Institute of Outdoor Advertising Cordially Invites You..., 1988 (Box 17)
      - 10A Regional Reference 1982/1983, circa 1982-1983 (Box 17)
      - Just the Right Size: Canon, undated (Box 17)
      - Make Your Advertising A Show Stopper, undated (Box 17)
      - Market Efficiency, circa 1975-1976 (Box 17)
      - Market Reach, undated (Box 17)
      - Mileage Manager, undated (Box 17)
      - Mixed Media Marriages II, undated (Box 17)
      - My Broker Is Paul Garnett..., undated (Box 17)
      - New Creative Guide to Outdoor Advertising, undated (Box 17)
      - ...None Has the Impact of Outdoor, undated (Box 17)
      - Obie 85, circa 1985-1986 (Box 17)
      - Our Agency's Creative Thinking Starts with Outdoor, undated (Box 17)
      - Our Outdoor Advertising Pays Off for Us, undated (Box 17)
      - Our Outdoor Introduction Has Made Us Instant Believers, undated (Box 17)
      - Our Revenue Doubled In Six Months, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor Advertising, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor Advertising for Political Candidates, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor And Cooperative Advertising, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor Energizes Gatorade, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor Is Dynamite, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor Has Been Our #1 Medium for 16 Years Because It Sells, 1976 Jan. (Box 17)
      - Outdoor Is Like a Giant Calling Card for Our Agency, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor! No Other Medium Has Created Such Dealer Response, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor's Finest: The Collection of 1982 Obie Award Winners, circa 1982-1983 (Box 17)
      - Outdoor... Sells Our Prospects, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor Spoken Here..., undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor: Showcase of Selectivity, undated (Box 17)
      - Outdoor: The Media's Medium (Box 17)
      - Peace, Happiness, Joy, undated (Box 17)
      - Perfect Fit: Levi's, Outdoor & TV, undated (Box 17)
      - Presenting the 1986 Obie Awards, 1986 (Box 17)
      - Presenting the 1987 Obie Awards, 1987 (Box 17)
      - Reason for Participating, undated (Box 17)
      - Sales Effectiveness Test..., undated (Box 17)
      - Selling More Indoors: Outdoors, undated (Box 17)
      - She was Crowned Miss America 1975, circa 1976 (Box 17)
      - Take A Step In the Right Direction..., undated (Box 17)
      - Tempt Taste Buds, undated (Box 17)
      - They Called Outdoor An Eyesore Until..., undated (Box 17)
      - Tools of the Trade, 1987 May (Box 17)
      - Using Only Outdoor, 1977 Mar. (Box 17)
      - Warning: Classified Information Contained Inside, undated (Box 17)
      - We Create Lots of Interest, undated (Box 17)
      - We Deliver the Good for Packaged Goods, undated (Box 17)
      - We're #1 in the Sun Market, 1974 Sept. (Box 17)
      - We've Increased Our Outdoor, 1977 Oct. (Box 17)
      - What Do You Get for Your Money in Outdoor, circa 1982 (Box 17)
      - What Do You Get for Your Money in Outdoor, circa 1988 (Box 17)
      - When Our Outdoor Goes Up, Our Sales Go Up. Every Time, 1977 June (Box 17)
      - When Our Outdoor Posters Go Up, Orders Start to Jump, 1977 Dec. (Box 17)
      - When People Go Buy, Outdoor Sells, undated (Box 17)
      - When You Need A Strong Pitch..., undated (Box 17)
      - Why Has the Airline..., undated (Box 17)
      - With Outdoor... Insurance In Force Has Doubled, undated (Box 17)
      - With Outdoor Our Number One Medium, 1977 Dec. (Box 17)
      - With Outdoor Our Only Medium, 1976 June (Box 17)
      - With Outdoor...Our Sales And profits Are Now At All-time Highs, 1977 Feb. (Box 17)
      - With Outdoor's Great Impact, We're Gaining Share of Market, 1977 Dec. (Box 17)
      - With Outdoor We Broke All Our Previous Attendance Records, 1977 Apr. (Box 17)
      - With Outdoor, We Had Sales Increases of 33% and 35%, 1976 Nov. (Box 17)
      - 35th National Competition of Outdoor Advertising Art, circa 1967 (Box 17)
      - 36th Outdoor Advertising Competition, circa 1968 (Box 17)
      - 9th Outdoor Advertising Competition, circa 1971 (Box 17)
    - IOA press reproductions, circa 1984 (Box 17)
    - IOA promotional material (notebook), undated, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 17)
    - IOA promotional material (notebook), undated (continued), (2 of 2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Metromedia Technologies, 1988-1990 and undated, (5 folders)
    [Contains memos, sales meeting files, client lists, slides and a photograph album.]
    - Booklet, Visual Excellence, undated (Box 18)
    - National Sales Meeting binder, 1988 (Box 18)
    - National Sales Meeting binder, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - National Sales Meeting binder, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Photograph album, 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1985-1988 and undated
    - ABC--Representing Out-of-Home Media Nationwide, 1988 Feb. 22 (Box 19)
    - A. C. Nielson Outdoor Advertising Research Highlights, undated (Box 19)
    - Business Products, undated (Box 19)
    - Compass Data Selection File, 1988 Oct. 20, undated (Box 19)
    - Co-Op Alert!, undated (Box 19)
    - Double Your Ad Budget with Outdoor Co-Op!, undated (Box 19)
    - Gannett Outdoor Group, undated (Box 19)
    - [Gannett Outdoor Network USA Guide to Out-of-Home, 1993; item located with Oversized Material] (Box 19)
    - Foglio Base, 1985 Oct. 4, undated (Box 19)
    - Glossary, undated (Box 19)
    - How to Advertise Financial Products & Services, undated (Box 19)
    - How to Advertise Food, undated (Box 19)
    - How to Market & Advertise Travel & tourism, undated (Box 19)
    - Innovative Solutions Through Out-of-home Communications, undated (Box 19)
    - Inside Outdoor: Back to the Basics, undated (Box 19)
    - [Kraft--Picture of Freshness, 1979; item located with Oversized Material] (Box 19)
    - Life's a Little Fresher with Dole, undated (Box 19)
    - A Look at Outdoor Production, undated (Box 19)
    - The Morris Communicator, undated (Box 19)
    - Naegele Outdoor Advertising, undated (Box 19)
    - Nike Sportswear, undated (Box 19)
    - No Other Medium Pinpoints Your Market More Accurately, undated (Box 19)
    - Not Just a Lot of Hot Air, undated (Box 19)
    - Outdoor Advertising Market Guide, undated (Box 19)
    - Planning for Out-of-home Media, undated (Box 19)
    - Pocket Distance Finder--Painted Bulletin, undated (Box 19)
    - Pocket Distance Finder--20 Sheet Poster, undated (Box 19)
    - Pocket Distance Finder--30 Sheet Poster, undated (Box 19)
    - Touchdown for Health--Milk, undated (Box 19)
    - [The Unbreakables, undated; item located with Oversized Material] (Box 19)
    - What Do More Than 350 Advertising Agencies..., undated (Box 19)
    - When People Go Buy, Outdoor Sells, undated (Box 19)
    - Who, What, When, and Where?, undated (Box 19)
  - Outdoor Advertising Association of America, 1988-1998 and undated
    - OAAA Centennial Convention, 1991 (Box 20)
    - OAAA Marketing Division -- Idea Bank Map, undated (Box 20)
    - OAAA membership roster, 1996-1998 (Box 20)
    - Outdoor America, undated (Box 20)
    - Outdoor case studies, undated (Box 20)
    - Outdoor, It's Not a Medium, It's a Large, undated (Box 20)
    - Outdoor, It's Not a Medium, It's a Large: Automotive presentation script, undated (Box 20)
    - Outdoor, It's Not a Medium, It's a Large: Grocery store presentation script, undated (Box 20)
    - Outdoor, It's Not a Medium, It's a Large: Presentation manual, undated (Box 20)
    - Outdoor, It's Not a Medium, It's a Large: Presentation script, undated (Box 20)
    - 1988 Obie Awards, undated (Box 20)
    - 1989 Obie Awards, undated (Box 20)
    - 1989 Obie book--letter and order form, undated (Box 20)
    - 1994 Obie Awards, undated (Box 20)
    - 1994 Obie Awards--official call for entries, undated (Box 20)
    - 1994 Obie awards--program, undated (Box 20)
  - Outdoor Network USA, 1988-1998 and undated
    - Another American Revolution, undated (Box 20)
    - Black Outdoor--The Inside Solution, undated (Box 20)
    - Heat Up Your Advertising, undated (Box 20)
    - Get Them While They're Hot, undated (Box 20)
    - How to Create a Masterpiece, undated (Box 20)
    - Knock 'Em Out, undated (Box 20)
    - The Sweet Smell of Success, undated (Box 20)
    - Well Connected, undated (Box 20)
    - 1987 Rate Card, circa 1987 (Box 20)
    - 1988 Rate Card, circa 1988 (Box 20)
    - 1989 Rate Card, circa 1989 (Box 20)
  - Patrick Media Group, 1987-1988 and undated
    - Impressions, 1988 (Box 20)
    - Impressions, 1987 (Box 20)
    - Legibility guide, undated (Box 20)
    - Pacific Bell Smart Yellow Pages Just Got Smarter, undated (Box 20)
  - Traffic Audit Bureau, 1987-1998 and undated
    - Planning for Out-of-Home Media, 1987 (Box 20)
    - 1993 annual conference attendees, circa 1993 (Box 20)
    - 1994 TAB Conference, circa 1994 (Box 20)
    - '95 TAB Conference, circa 1995 (Box 20)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1984-1998, (3 Boxes)
  Contains audio-visual materials, mostly video cassettes, from a variety of producers. Most items are related to advertising and outdoor advertising. Organized alphabetically by producer and title.
  - Action Ads. VHS. TRT: about 5:00 minutes. undated (Box 21)
  - Advantisers. Scrolling Mobile Billboards from Advantisers. VHS. TRT: about 3:00. undated (Box 21)
  - DETV, Diversity Entertainment Television. Marketing demo. VHS. TRT: 2:40. undated (Box 21)
    [3 copies]
  - Donrey Media Group. Donrey Basics. VHS. TRT: 11:30. undated (Box 21)
  - John Evans Co./The Orton Group. The Great Outdoors. VHS. TRT: 11:00. undated (Box 21)
  - Federal Sign. The Federal Sign Advantage. VHS. TRT: 6:13. 1989 May 23 (Box 21)
  - Federal Sign. Value Added Leasing. VHS. TRT: 7:00. 1990 Sept. 11 (Box 21)
  - Gannett Outdoor Group. Masterwork. Umatic. TRT: 19:16. undated (Box 21)
  - Gannett Outdoor Group. Superflex--A new Dimension in Creative Outdoor. VHS. TRT: 8:00. undated (Box 21)
  - Greyhound Lines, Inc. Bus wrap Program. VHS. TRT: 6:30. 1997 Aug. 8 (Box 21)
  - Greyhound Lines, Inc. Bus wrap Program. VHS. TRT: 6:30. 1997 Oct. 17 (Box 21)
  - Human Performance Training, Inc. A Revolution in Learning: Go for Baroque. VHS. TRT: about 30:00. undated (Box 21)
  - Integrated Systems Engineering. Innovator and Product Leader. VHS. TRT: about 5:00. undated (Box 21)
  - Institute for Outdoor Advertising. But Nobody Knew Her Name. VHS. TRT: about 5:00. undated (Box 21)
  - IOA. Obie Awards 1994 finalists--multi-image transfer. VHS. TRT: 5:30. undated (Box 21)
  - IOA. 1987 Obie Awards. VHS. TRT: 14:00. circa 1987. (Box 21)
    [2 copies]
  - IOA. 1987 Obie Awards. Umatic. TRT: 14:00. circa 1987. (Box 21)
  - IOA. 1992 Obies. VHS. TRT: about 10:00. circa 1992. (Box 21)
  - Legend Productions. TDI Corporate Sales Video. VHS. TRT: 5:02. 1990 Feb. 5. (Box 21)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour. Billboards. VHS. TRT: 16:00. 1985 July 31. (Box 21)
  - Media Enterprises, Inc./Adweek. Out-of-Home: What's Next. VHS. TRT: 6:25. 1993 Apr. 6. (Box 21)
  - Metromedia Technologies. Bringing Outdoor Advertising to Life. Umatic. TRT: 5:21. 1989 Dec. 29. (Box 21)
  - Metromedia Technologies. Details, Details. VHS. TRT: 8:10. 1993 Oct. 1. (Box 21)
  - Metromedia Technologies. Faces That Stand Out in a Crowd. VHS. TRT: 7:00. 1991 May 13. (Box 21)
  - Metromedia Technologies. Metromedia Technologies. VHS. TRT: 16:00. undated (Box 21)
  - Metromedia Technologies. One Name Says It All. VHS. TRT: 7:25. 1997 June 19. (Box 21)
  - Metromedia Technologies. MMT slide presentation. Audio Cassette. TRT: about 30:00. undated (Box 21)
  - Metromedia Technologies. Street Smart. VHS. TRT: 22:30. undated (Box 22)
  - Metrovision of North America, Inc. computer channel demo. VHS. TRT: 7:45. 1992 Apr. (Box 22)
  - Multimedia Technologies, Inc. Atlanta Spectacular. VHS. TRT: about 3:00. undated (Box 22)
  - Naegele. The New Messenger. VHS. TRT: unknown. undated (Box 22)
  - Naegele. Windows. VHS. TRT: unknown. undated (Box 22)
  - Nevada Bell. Billboard story from news from Nevada Bell. VHS. TRT: 1:10. undated (Box 22)
  - OAAA. Building Brands Beautifully. VHS. TRT: 3:00. 1997 Nov. (Box 22)
  - OAAA. Outdoor: It's Not a Medium, It's a Large. VHS. TRT: 10:00. 1993. (Box 22)
  - OAAA. Simpler Age; Smaller Business; Survey; New Standards. VHS. TRT: about 2:30. undated (Box 22)